export const game = [
  {
    question: "Which character is a paleontologist?",
    answer: "Ross",
    wrongAnswers: ["Chandler", "Joey", "Rachel"],
  },
  {
    question: "What is the name of Rachel's boss at Ralph Lauren?",
    answer: "Mr. Zelner",
    wrongAnswers: ["Mr. Waltham", "Mr. Stevens", "Mr. Green"],
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which character said the line, 'It's like all my life everyone has always told me, 'You're a shoe! You're a shoe! You're a shoe!' Well, what if I don't want to be a shoe? What if I want to be a purse, you know, or a hat!'?",
    answer: "Rachel",
    wrongAnswers: ["Monica", "Phoebe", "Chandler"],
  },
  {
    question: "What is the name of Ross and Monica's parents?",
    answer: "Jack and Judy",
    wrongAnswers: ["Frank and Alice", "Richard and Nora", "Bob and Helen"],
  },
  {
    question: "Which character introduces Phoebe to Mike?",
    answer: "Joey",
    wrongAnswers: ["Ross", "Chandler", "Rachel"],
  },
  {
    question: "Who was Monica's boyfriend who is also a periodontist?",
    answer: "Dr. Richard Burke",
    wrongAnswers: ["Pete Becker", "Dr. Barry Farber", "Chandler Bing"],
  },
  {
    question: "What is the name of the game show Joey auditions for?",
    answer: "Bamboozled",
    wrongAnswers: ["Mystified", "Baffled", "Dazed"],
  },
  {
    question: "What was the name of Ross's first wife?",
    answer: "Carol",
    wrongAnswers: ["Susan", "Emily", "Rachel"],
  },
  {
    question: "Which friend accidentally leaves a baby on a bus?",
    answer: "Ross",
    wrongAnswers: ["Chandler", "Joey", "Monica"],
  },
  {
    question: "What does Chandler's co-worker Bob think his name is?",
    answer: "Toby",
    wrongAnswers: ["Charley", "Barry", "Marty"],
  },
]
